

MY CONTACT

(+84) 93 882 6364

11/02/1994

125 Thoi Hoa, Vinh Loc A, Binh Chanh, Ho Chi Minh City

https://lngkhanh94.github.io

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Strong communication skills
- Good experience in teamwork skills
- Analytical and problem-solving skills
- Management and planning skills
- Partner communication skills
- Farther communication skill
- Presentation skills
- Reflection skills

REFERENCE

Tien, Nguyen Manh (Mr.)

Email: tiennm15494@sacombank.com

Phone: (+84) 986 733 782

KHANH, LE NGOC

TECHNICAL LEAD

ABOUT MF

I have seven years of software development and management experience, including three years in the roles of technical lead and project manager. My goal is to become a project management expert in the near future and become a future project manager

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

March 2019 - Present

Technical Lead of Application Development Center worker in Sai Gon Thuong Tin Commercial Joint Stock Bank

Key responsibilities:

- Manage the tasks and work progress of the team as a team leader.
- Reviewing design, technical, and operational solution documents related to the bank's online payment transactions.
- Participating in the development of projects to build new banking systems on the basis of micro-services and optimizing existing systems
- Provide a technical approach to software development that addresses business features; write overview architectural documents and coding conventions; manage teams; and guide developers to develop detailed blueprints for each function.
- Using technology to manage teams and projects Microsoft Project, Jira

August 2016 to March 2019

Senior System Development and Integration of Application Development Center worker in Saigon Thuong Tin Commercial Joint Stock Bank

Key responsibilities:

- Design and develop internal service applications that handle reporting requests from the business and integrate third-party applications and external services.
- Implement software development requirements and design an online transaction application system for Ecom, QR, POS, Ewallet, ATM, Card Service Bus, Integrated Core Card, and T24 Bank.
- Design and develop on-demand and integrated services with fintech organizations (Zalo, MoMo, etc.), domestic card organizations (Napas), and international Cybersource/Visa/Master.

TECHNOLOGY

Languages:

- C# ASP.NET (.Net/Core)
- C/C++
- Java
- NodeJs
- ReactJS
- PHP

Database

- Microsoft SQL Server,
- IBM DB2
- Oracle

Server:

- Windows Server
- Unix

Cache:

- Memory
- Redis

Proxy:

- Apache
- Nginx

Protocol

- HTTP/HTTPs
- TCP
- Socket
- SMTP
- FTP/FTPs/SFTP

Environment:

- Kubernetes/Docker/Container
- OpenShift

Source control:

- GitHub/GitLab
- Tortoise-SVN

Plan:

- Microsoft Project
- Jira/Confluence

Model:

- Agile/Scrum
- Waterfall

- Design system models to ensure continuous, stable, stateless, and scalable operation, with a mechanism to reduce the load on the system and database.
- Design responsive systems to switch between async and sync processing streams, have error handling mechanisms, and timeout when backend systems fail.
- The intensive programming language C# handles and solves mechanisms for multitasking, multithreading, memory leaks, high CPUs, and threads.
- Implement and participate in the development of integration axes: message queue, web or application server, caching, workflow orchestration, load balancer.

January 2016 to March 2016

- Junior System Development at Thai Son Technology Development Company
- Key responsibilities:
- Implemented in-house application software development using technology based on .Net platform using WinForms and Windows services

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

- · Industrial University of Ho Chi Minh City
- Specialization in Information Technology
- I have participated in courses organized by FSOFT FPT [2015].
- I have participated in classes on web design faculty and courses organized by IBM [2014].

Completed in 2016

ACHIEVEMENTS

2022 - Project Management Certification FMIT PMI

2019 - Certificate of Completion of AWS Courses

2016 - ICTCC conference paper on MCPGA